Credential life insurance.
>> Life insurance
[Music]
for almost 177 years. African
bankial
life insurance company.
insurance
20,000 30,000 50,000 100,000 200,000
policy
Insurance.
insurance.
First one, prudent life plan,
kidney problem, cancer,
heart, heart transplant,
critical illnesses, heart
insurance
100,000 Ghana cities
200,000 500,000 a million Ghana series
and more
disability.
At
least
access to free medical checkup.
hospital.
Free annual medical check.
[Music]
5 years, 6 years, 8 years
insurance policy.
Wow.
man saychech.
Towers
househ
[Music]
insurance.
Okay. So, what I'll talk about is the
recruitment opportunity we give to young
graduates who are not working, who are
currently unemployed. We have a job
opportunity. It is a who were around or
you know someone who is on currently
unemployed, you can recommend the person
to take the employment opportunity.